dinartrade.com 2019-11-01

# Privacy Policy « XCHANGE OF AMERICA

**What Personal Information Does Xchange of America Gather About Me?**

The information we learn about our consumers helps us improve our products and services and make your experience a better one.  Here are the types of information we might gather.

We receive and store any information you enter on xchangeofamerica.com or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for purposes as responding to our customers requests, specializing features, improving online experience and physical stores, and communicating with you. We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail.

**Cookies**

Cookies are unique identifiers that we transfer to your device to enable our systems to recognize your device and to provide features.

The Help feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. 

**Does Xchange of America share information it gathers?**

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and will not sell it to others. We share customer information only within the Xchange of America family.  Because we are a licensed financial institution customer information is highly protected. We comply with the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act and will update customers to any changes to our information sharing policy.  

**Protection of Xchange of America and Release of Personal Data**

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law.

**How Secure is My Info?**

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. 

**Conditions**

If you choose to visit xchangeofamerica.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Florida. If you have any concern about privacy at XchangeofAmerica.com, please email us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly and our Privacy Notice will change also. Please view our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

**Information You Give Us**

You provide information when you search, buy, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service.

**Record Retention**

We only keep your records to the extent of this Privacy Policy or in some cases which is required by law as a financial institution.

**Third Party Websites**

We have links to third party websites and it’s your responsibility to read their Privacy Policy as the Xchange of America policy does not apply.

**Protecting Your Personal Information**

Here at Xchange of America protecting your personal information is of the highest priority.  Background checks of all employees are administered and confidentiality agreements are signed prior to being hired.

We constantly review our procedures to improve your online and store experience.
